havetherelationshipyouwant.com 2019-12-21

# Have The Relationship You Want | Your Privacy

Effective date: March 23, 2018

Amare Inc. ("Us", "We", or "Our") operates the www.havetherelationshipyouwant.com website (the "Service") on behalf of Rori Raye and Have The Relationship You Want.

We will never sell, rent or use your personal information in any way other than outlined in this page. We have a No Spam policy, meaning We will not allow third parties (unless outlined in this policy) to message you, nor will we rent out or sell your information for other companies' use.

We respect your information and always make our best effort to protect and secure it. This page outlines Our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Data when you use our Service, and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this page have the same meanings as in Our Terms and Conditions.

## Definitions

#### Personal Data

Personal Data is any information relating to a natural person who can be identified, either directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier. An identifier may include, but is not limited to, a name, email, address, credit card and/or IP address.

#### Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

#### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

#### Data Controller

Data Controller means a person or entity who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any Personal Data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, We are a Data Controller of your data.

#### Data Processor (or Service Provider)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person or entity (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

#### Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

#### User

The User is the individual using Our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

## Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve Our Service to you.

#### Personal Data

While using Our Service, We may ask you to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email Address and Name - provided by you when registering to receive Our free newsletters or when purchasing Our products
  * Address, City, State/Province, Postal Code, Phone and Credit Card Information \- provided by you when purchasing Our products
  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to send you newsletters, marketing or promotional materials that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by visiting our unsubscribe page or following the instructions provided at the bottom of emails We send.

We will never sell your Personal Data to third parties or use it for purposes other than what is described in this page.

#### Usage Data

We may collect information on how you access and use this Service ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of Our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar technologies to track the activity on Our Service and maintain certain information about Our users.

Cookies are files with small amounts of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze Our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of Our Service.

Examples of Cookies We use:

  * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to provide Our Service and give you access to paid programs.
  * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.

For more information on Our use of cookies, visit the Cookies Policy page.

## Use of Data

Amare Inc. uses data We collect for various purposes including:

  * To provide and maintain Our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of Our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that We can improve Our Service
  * To monitor the usage of Our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which We offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information
  * To notify you about changes to Our Service

## Retention of Data

Amare Inc. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with Our legal obligations (for example, if We are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce Our legal agreements and policies.

Amare Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

## Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Amare Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure Of Data

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Amare Inc. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

Amare Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Amare Inc.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## "Do Not Track" Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

## Your Rights

Amare Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Please contact Us to make any required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data We hold about you and if you want it to be removed from Our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data We hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Amare Inc. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that We may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

## Service Providers

We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate Our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on Our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist Us in analyzing how Our Service is used.

These third parties may have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on Our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to monitor and analyze the use of Our Service.

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of Our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Customer Support

We use the Zendesk customer support platform to assist Us in helping users of Our Service. Zendesk has access to Service data that has been shared by a User with Our customer support team. Zendesk is operated by Zendesk, Inc.

You can learn more about Zendesk's privacy practices and policies by visiting [Zendesk's Privacy Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/).

### Email

We use the Responsys email platform ("Email Provider") to deliver Our newsletter, purchase receipts and other promotional emails. Responsys has access to Service data relevant to your activity and purchases within Our Service. Responsys is a platform operated by Oracle Corporation.

We have a No Spam policy, meaning We will not allow any third parties, other than the Email Providers listed in this page, to message you. We will never sell or rent out your information.

You can learn more about Responsys' privacy practices and policies by visiting [Responsys' Privacy Policy](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/privacy-policy.html).

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, We use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

When paying for a product We may store or collect your payment card details. That information is also provided directly to Our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. We along with Our payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors We work with are:

  * Merchant e-Solutions - [Merchant e-Solution's Privacy Policy](https://www.merchante-solutions.com/privacy-policy/)

  * PayPal - [Paypal's Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

### Profile-Based Advertising

We may use the following third-party vendors to create demographic User profiles using the Personal Data you share with Us when you sign up for an email newsletter or purchase our products. In such circumstances, the information We share will only be used to market our Services to you and other similar users.

  * Facebook - [Facebook's Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

  * Google - [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

  * Pinterest - [Pinterest's Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)

  * Twitter - [Twitter's Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)

### Remarketing

We may use the following behavioral remarketing services to advertise on third-party websites to you after you visited Our Service. We and Our third-party vendors may use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to Our Service.

  * Facebook - [Facebook's Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). To opt-out of Facebook's interest-based ads, visit [Facebook's instructions](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217).

  * Google - [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). To opt-out of Google Display Network ads, visit [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

  * Pinterest - [Pinterest's Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy). To opt-out of Pinterest's interest-based ads, visit [Pinterest's instructions](http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data).

  * Twitter - [Twitter's Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy). To opt-out of Twitter's interest-based ads, visit [Twitter's instructions](https://business.twitter.com/en/help/ads-policies/other-policy-requirements/interest-based-opt-out-policy.html).

### Website Hosting & Service Data

We use the Amazon Web Services ("AWS") platform to host Our Service as well as store Service data. AWS is provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc.

You can learn more about AWS's privacy practices and policies by visiting [AWS's Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/).

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

You must be 18 or older to enter Our website. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided Us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that We have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from Our servers.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Us by:

  * Visiting the contact page
  * Sending a letter to:

Amare Inc.  
Attn: "Have The Relationship You Want" Support Team  
9450 SW Gemini Dr. #95558  
Beaverton, OR 97008-7105
